Contact

moben6@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/christelleoben-rn-bsn-48682050 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Medication Administration
Wound Care
Patient Education

Languages

French

English (Native or Bilingual)

Honors-Awards

National Honor Society

Christelle Oben RN, BSN

Experienced Nurse

Saint Johns, Florida

Summary

Experienced pediatric and adult Dialysis and Emergency Room Nurse with a demonstrated history of working in the hospital & health care industry. Skilled in Medication Administration, Critical Care, Healthcare Management, Healthcare, and Clinical Research. Strong healthcare services professional with a Master's degree focused in Family Practice Nurse/Nursing from Walden University.

Experience

Aurora Health Care Travel Registered Nurse September 2018 - Present (1 year 10 months)

Greater Milwaukee Area

Baltimore, Maryland

I currently work as an acute dialysis nurse, servicing 10 local hospital within the Aurora health umbrella.

Fresenius Medical Care North America Charge Nurse November 2016 - Present (3 years 8 months)

I currently work as a charge nurse in an outpatient dialysis clinic taking care of both pediatric and adult

MAS staffing
Travel Nurse
October 2015 - Present (4 years 9 months)

Florida Hospital Travel Registered Nurse August 2017 - September 2018 (1 year 2 months) Orlando, Florida Area

I worked as an acute care dialysis nurse

St Agnes Hospital

Emergency Room RN

September 2014 - May 2018 (3 years 9 months)

Baltimore, Maryland Area

I worked as an Emergency room nurse in our pediatric and adult ED providing care to the western Baltimore area

National Institutes of Health Clinical Research Nurse March 2016 - January 2017 (11 months)

Bethesda, Maryland

Chesapeake Medical Staffing and Home Care

RN

April 2015 - April 2016 (1 year 1 month)

Work as a travel nurse and prn nurse

- -National Spine and Pain Centers, LLC
- -Bayview Hospital

Maxim Healthcare Services

Pediatric RN

May 2014 - January 2016 (1 year 9 months)

Falls Church, Va

Work as a pediatric nurse providing providing care to help maximize their recovery in home.

American Care Partners @ Home, Inc.

4 years 3 months

Pediatric RN

May 2014 - January 2016 (1 year 9 months)

Falls Church, Virginia

I provid needed care to clients in their homes to maximize their recovery, quality of life and enable seniors, individuals with disabilities, special needs pediatrics and individuals living with chronic conditions to remain safe, functional and comfortable in the place they choose to live and avoid institutional placement.

LPN

November 2011 - May 2014 (2 years 7 months)

Falls Church, VA

I provide needed care to clients in their homes to maximize their recovery, quality of life and enable seniors, individuals with disabilities, special needs

pediatrics and individuals living with chronic conditions to remain safe, functional and comfortable in the place they choose to live and avoid institutional placement.

Maxim Healthcare Services

LPN

November 2011 - December 2013 (2 years 2 months)

Falls Church, VA

Work as a pediatric nurse providing providing care to help maximize their recovery in home.

Strategic Resources, Inc. (SRI)

Pediatric RN

April 2012 - May 2013 (1 year 2 months)

McLean Virginia

Provide respite services to Military families in Ft Meade, Ft Belvoir, and the Pentagon.

Fauquier Hospital

LPN

June 2011 - 2013 (2 years)

Warrenton, VA

Montgomery Home Care

LPN

April 2010 - 2013 (3 years)

Rockville, MD

Worked in home providing care to the geriatric population.

- Medication administrations and reminders

-ADL'S

Education

Walden University

Master's degree, Family Practice Nurse/Nursing · (2016 - 2020)

Stratford University

Bachelor of Science (BS), Registered Nursing/Registered

Nurse · (2012 - 2014)

Virginia School of Nursing

LPN, Nursing Practice · (2008 - 2009)

Eleanor Roosevelt

· (2001 - 2005)

Eleanor Roosevelt

High School Diploma, High School/Secondary Diplomas and Certificates · (2001 - 2005)